[Music]
hello I'm Grant grunder Schmid producer
of review with Faris mcneel as you know
our season 1 finale ended with fars
punching me and then storming off in a
huff what you may not know is that we
haven't seen nor heard from him since
then he's vanished bygones are bygones
and we just want him back so we're
appealing to you the public to help
spread awareness of this missing TV host
by using the hashtag find Forest that's
Forest with two RS this is not a joke or
a publicity stunt it's an honest
appeal won't you help bring Forest
McNeil back to review and then back to
you where he belongs thank
you good and you can put the hashtag at
the bottom of the screen yeah
[Music]
okay